Today we're making this amazing one minute microwave cookie. This is not a
mug cookie, this is not a sad cookie. This is the proper delicious microwave
cookie. I really wanted to develop a recipe for you that was quick and
amazing. Once you try this you'll always be making one minute chocolate chip
cookie. Okay so we're gonna start out with some good old butter which we're
gonna melt in the microwave. To this we're gonna add some brown sugar and a
dash of milk which you'll see in a moment. I do not like to add eggs to any
of my microwave recipes. You know this eggs in the microwave usually become
rubbery and we don't like to eat rubber. Not on my channel okay? So we're gonna
substitute the eggs with a dash of milk. If you're new to my channel, hello there
welcome. Make sure to subscribe and click that notification bell. I post new
videos every week. I've gone ahead and added the dry ingredients which are just
flour, baking soda and salt and you want to mix these just until combined. Now I'm
using chocolate chunks today. I've just cut up you know a chocolate bar. You can
use chocolate chips. Use whatever you like. You're going to fold these into the
dough and then you're gonna bring the dough together with your hands and shape
it into a cookie. So form a ball and press a depth. Place it onto some parchment
paper. Add more chocolate chips if you like and this is done. Well this is not
done you know you guys. Okay we're ready to microwave this. Now I'm gonna speed up
the video but I do want to mention two important things. You're going to cook
your cookie for exactly one minute. However every microwave is different so
just know that your cookie could take between one minute and one minute and
15 seconds. The second most important thing to know is to not overcook your
cookie. Your cookie should come out of the microwave still soft. As you can see
when you pick it up it's gonna be really soft. So let this cool for about five
minutes otherwise it's gonna be too hot to handle and the cookie will just fall
apart. How amazing does this look? You would think this was made in a regular
oven. If you love warm soft baked cookies you have to try this. This is
gooey, delicious and satisfying. Make this for late night craving after school,
after work. Have this with ice cream. You'll love it.