It's a great big world.
We're so much to lear.
We're pasionately geographic kids.
Hey everyone, it's Kai again.
I'm back with another amazing episode of Not Geo Kids.
And this week we're talking all about robots.
Okay, so I bet you're wondering, what exactly is a robot?
Good question.
Basicaly, a robot is a machine created to perform a series of actions.
This actions could be as simple as roaming around the house vacuming up dirty floors.
While other robots perform more complicated tasks such as traveling to and exploring different planets like NASA's Mars Exploration Robots,
which were build to study the surface of Mars.
And did you know that humans have been building robots for centuries?
In fact, many believed the first robot was created over 200 years ago in ancient Greece by a man named Architea.
Architea built a bird-like self-repeling machine that could fly up to a distance of 200 meters.
That's like two football fields.
Today, robots come in all shapes and sizes.
Same are small, even microscopic, while others are large.
In some cases, as big as a car or even a truck.
They are flying robots, robots can drive, and robots that can swim.
Robots can do a lot of things.
Who knows?
Maybe one day robots will be able to do just about everything that humans can doo.
Scientists think so.
To get us started, let's take a look at this first set of videos where we learn a little bit more about robots.