Welcame back to the baby gemas. We've got it all for you. The struggles. Oh, the intensity.
The triumphs. First up, gymnastics. The American. Working it. Just look at that concetration.
Ten meter total. One of the marquae events at any baby game. And there they go.
China running away with it.
Looks like he's stuck on the line. And here comes Argentina on the outside.
But China does it for gold.
Back to gymnastics. Japan on the rings. Pressure has never been higher.
What an affort.
Now the American.
The discount. Nailed it.
Gold for the US. Over to weightlifting. Argentina. Can they do it?
Oh, and it's a heartbreking result.
Now the German is just snowboating.
Now onto our final event, the three-purtle total. There they go.
A little unorthodox. France having some trouble on the last hurdle.
Oh, and it's incredible. It's gold for France.
Watch all your favorite Olympic moments on the Olympic Channel, where the game's never-end.