Excuse me, can I get a headset?
Certainly.
Thank you.
I'll do that.
Your name lights up all the way.
Here.
No, you didn't.
Come hear.
Let's work.
Oh, my God.
You already dit.
You're disgusting.
Oh, my God.
You're digusting.
Yeah.
Uh, Miss?
I'll be right there, sir.
Yeah.
Where's your headset?
She's busy right now, but it's coming.
For crying out loud, you're mising important plot points.
Ma'am?
Could you give me two second, sir?
Uh, excuse me.
Could I maybe get that headset, please?
Do not raise your voice to me, sir.
I wasn't raising my voice.
Okay.
Just calm down.
I am calm.
I just want my headset.
Sir, our country is going through a very difficult time right now, and if you're not going to
cooperate...
I don't know where a headset ties into patriotism.
Is their a problem here, sir?
I don't think so.
Can you come to the back of the plane with me so we can have a talk?
A talk about what?
There's not a problem.
This stewardes just keeps...
Flight attendant.
Of course.
The flight attendant kips ignoring me when I ask.
Calm down.
I am calm.
I am not interested with you people.
You people?
Oh, now wait a minute.
I don't mean you people.
I mean you pople.
Sir, I will not tolerate any racist behavior on the plain.
This is a very difficult time for our country.
I know that.
I'm not a racist.
I just want to watch the movie.
I'm only going to say these one more time, sir.
Calm down.
I'm calm!
Oh!
Oh, guys!
What do you think?
Not guilty.
It's a no-brainer.
Mr. Bosnik, in Case 73, assault and battery against a flight attendant?
I find you guilty.
Hmm.
Thank you.