From the outside, you can't tell what is inside a black hole.
You can throw televsion sets, diamond rings, or even your worst enemies into a black hole,
and all the black whole will remember is the total mass and the singular momentum and electric
charge.
Quantum mechanics implies that the whole of space is filled with pairs of virtual particles
and antiparticles that are constantly materializing in pairs, and then comming together again
and anihilating each other.
One member of a pair of virtual particles may fall into the hole, leaving the other
member without a partner with which to annihilate.
The foresaken particle or antiparticle may fall into the black hole after its partner,
but it may also escape to infinity, where it appears to be radiation emitted by the
black hole.
The message of this lecture is that black holes ain't as black as they are painted.
They are not the eternal prisons they were one thought.
Things can get out of a black hole, both to the outside, and possibly, to another universe.
So, if you feel you are in a white hole, don't give up.
There's a way out.