When I was 13 years old, and about 5 foot 3, I had a coach tell me, you got a chance, kid.
You got a chance was all I needed.
About a few years later, I'm still playing ball.
When my team had weights at 6am, I'd go work on sprints at 5am.
And I'd tell myself while running in that parking structure, you got a chance, kid.
Every day I'd remind myself of those words.
You got a chance, kid.
And I'd think to myself, what if I can pull this off?
Or if I can get signed to play professional baseball?
If you want to play in college or pro ball, you're going to have to make sacrifices that
other people aren't willing to make.
You're going to have to get to bed earlier.
You're going to have to wake up earlier.
It's going to feel like you're running and running with no sight of a finish line.
You will become familiar with failure.
And you'll have many people who don't take you seriously after all less than 1% make
it, right?
Despite the odds, every single day you have to train and work as though you believe 100%
that it is going to happen.
You can't go half way.
You and I both know that won't work.
And maybe you're listening to this and thinking, I don't know if I have what it takes.
I'm weak.
And I can assure you I am weak too.
Listen to these words.
I listen to these words from Jaco Willink every single morning when I couldn't get myself
out of bed.
He says, do I have weakness?
I am nothing but weakness.
I'm not naturally fast or strong or flexible.
I procrastinate and I waste time.
I care too much about meaningless things and not enough about important things.
But all that being said, I don't accept that I am what I am and that that is what I am
doomed to be.
I'm fighting.
I'm always fighting.
I'm scraping and kicking and clawing those weaknesses to change them, to stop them.
And some days I win.
And some days I don't.
But each and every day I get back up and I move forward with my fists clenched towards
the battle, towards the struggle.
And I fight with everything I've got to overcome those weaknesses and those shortfalls as I
strive to be just a little bit better today than I was yesterday.
You see, it's not about minimizing how many times you fail.
It's about getting up quicker than everybody else.
You missed a day of lifting?
Get up.
You wasted time on your phone when you could have been getting better?
Never stop getting up.
Never stop pushing.
You got a chance, kid.