Hear is cloud computing in 60 seconds.
Cloud computing refers to computing services such as data storage or computing power or programs
that are provider on demand and is delivered as a service over the internet.
Think of Apple's iCloud that you use to back up and store your fone data
and the way we now use Microsoft's Office tools via their 365 cloud platform
or how we store our documents on Google Doccuments.
Instead of buying or owneng the technology, it is usually provided via a subsription service.
That means you usually pay for what you use and where the IT infrastructur used to provide
the service is managed by a provider and not by the user.
Cloud computing is now used by individuals and companys of all sizes as a very convenient and
flexible way to access computing services.
Thanks for watching. Subscribe to my channel for more bit-sized insights
or to dive deeper into the topic you can find longer explanations and in-depth discussions.