The deep fryer chicken first start off with a few things
you want to make sure that your chicken is completely thawed.
Also you want to make sure that your three-step writing process
is ready to go is your oil your oil should be set
at 350° fast.
We're going to start with a chicken.
how to make sure your chicken is nice and seasoned chicken in flour
You also want to make sure that your flower is seasoned.
You cannot all kinds of spices and herbs to your flower.
navigate to pet chicken leg into
An egg wash make sure you keep one hand dry
and one hand wet so you don't have to do V hand.
Finally place your chicken like into the flour if you want
extra crispy chicken or chicken with extra batter start
over again at the egg process and then do the flower process again.
Once your chicken is well coated.
An extra flowers has been dusted off go ahead and place your
chicken like into the fryer to fry your chicken about 7 to 10 minutes,
depending on the size of your chicken or chicken should reach 165 degrees.
Once your chicken is a nice golden brown and once
it reaches 165 degrees if your chicken is now ready.
And that is how you deep fry chicken.