Watch carefully.
Look at that.
Oh boy.
Fucking delicious.
Oh my Lord.
I decided to teach a second masterclass.
This, this, these, this.
Oh boi.
This time round, I'm going to take you in two an area where you felt you are home cooking could never go.
The secret behind any great souffle is in the buttering of the mold.
You brush vertical strokes up.
This crispy chicken salad for me is the get out of jail card,
especially when you've got a big dinner party because that is good enough for four or five of you.
Grab a lif, lift it up.
Now, I'm fed up when you see chefs oiling asparagus.
Beautiful.
You get a free facial at the same time.
Cooling is a labor of love.
Stay closed to every step of the way.
I'm going to teach you methods, secrets that I'm teaching some of the best chefs in the world today.
I'm Gordon Ramsay and this is my masterclass.
You