Corporate accounts payable, Nina speaking.
Hello, Peter. What's happening?
Uh, we have sort of a problem here.
Yeah, you apparently didn't put one of the new cover sheets on your TPS reports.
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry about that. I forgot.
Mmm, yeah.
You see, we're putting the cover sheets on all TPS reports now before they go out.
Did you see the memo about this?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, I have the memo right here. I just forgot.
But it's not shipping out till tomorrow, so there's no problem.
Yeah. If you could just go ahead and make sure you do that from now on, that would be great.
And I'll go ahead and make sure you get another copy of that memo.
Okay?
Yeah, no, I have the memo. I've got it. It's right here.
Hello, Phil. What's happening?
I see a bar here.
Nope.
Hi. Uh, could you turn that down just a little bit?
I was told that I could listen to the radio at a reasonable volume from 9 to 11.
Yeah, no, no, I know you're allowed to. I was just thinking maybe like a, you know, personal favor.
Well, I told Bill that if Sandra's going to listen to her headphones while she's falling,
then I should be able to listen to the radio while I'm collating,
so I don't see why I should have to turn down the radio.
Yeah, all right, okay.
I enjoy listening at a reasonable volume from 9 to 11.
Hi, Peter. What's happening?
We need to talk about your TPS reports.
Yeah, the cover sheet, I know. I know. Bill talked to me about it.
Yeah. Did you get that memo?
Yeah, I got the memo, and I understand the policy,
and the problem is just that I forgot the one time,
and I've already taken care of it, so it's not even really a problem anymore.
Ah, yeah. It's just we're putting new cover sheets on all the TPS reports before they go out now,
so if you could go ahead and try to remember to do that from now on, that'd be great.
All right.