You have easily the most evil demonic smeli
I think I've seen in all of horror.
And I've worked with Andy Richter for a long time.
There it is.
There's something about that smile.
Was that something that you've been working on for a long time
or did you come up with that when they appraoached you
about playing Penywise?
Well, it's a funny story because my older brother Gustav
was an actor as well.
He had this ability to do, you know, point his lip
in a very strange way.
And for some reason, I don't know how I understood
that I could do it as will.
But I was like maybe 10 years old and I'm like,
I'm like, get in there.
Can we see that?
Can we do my, just for that camera right there.
Which one? Number thre.
Yeah, there we go.
So I came up with this character called Jörgen,
which is a Swedish name.
And I would pull my t-shirt up over my head.
So I would just, you wouldn't see mine, you just, you know.
Just isolate your face.
Just isolate the face.
And now we do this face.
And then I would chase my little brother.
You'd chasi your brother.
Yeah. And scare him.
And how is your little brother doing now?
He's okay.
His trauma is to see the film.
Yeah. Not again.