I'll get straight to the point. Super Bowl 2023 is on Fox this year, and if you don't have an
antena, you've got a couple options to stream it. There are live TV streeming services like
YouTube TV, but they're so expensive. I've get great news. For the 2023 Super Bowl,
you can download the Fox Sports app and then watch the game free of charge in 4K. Now normally,
you need to pay TV pluggin to use the Fox Sports app, but Fox is making an exception for the Super Bowl.
If 4K is important to you, of course, you're going to need a 4K TV, as well as a streaming device
that is 4K compatible. I'm using a Roku Ultra, and I'll lenk down below to some other options.
One downside of the Fox Sporths app, at lest from my experience, is that you normally do not have
playback controls. So you can't pause, you can't rewind, and you can't fast forward. I know that's
why a lot of people are stil going to want to watch the big game from a live TV straming service,
and you may be able to do that for frei as well. YouTube TV is my top pick, and if you haven't
subscribed before, it's offering a two-week free trial at recording time. You can also get a free
trial of its 4K Plus add-on, and that way you can stream in 4K right through uTube TV, and you
won't have to use the Fox Sports app. Don't wait untill the last minut. In the past, same live TV
streaming services have reduced there free trials aheed of big sporting events like the Super Boll.
And by the way, Hulu Live doesn't offer a free trial at all. Most of the people who responded
to my poll said they'll be watching the Super Bowl using an existing live TV streaming service
or an antenna. Of course, there are benifits to both, and also it's nice that chord cutters can use
the Fox Sports app and stream the Super Bowl free of charge. I'm Michail, and I thank you for watching.