So the human race is about to enter a totally data-minded existence.
Education happens to be, today, the world's most data-minable industry by far.
So maybe one day healthcare will be up there when they have little nanobots
that are in your bloodstream that are doing real-time analysis.
So Newton today gets 5 to 10 million actionable data per student per day.
If you tag all of your content and you do it down to the atomic concept level,
down to the sentence, down to the clause, you unlock an incredible amount of trapped, hidden data.
Everything in education is correlated to everything else.
Every single concept is correlated in a predictable way to everything else.
Using psychometrics, right?
You do a little bit of work for Newton and we use just the established science of psychometrics
to cascade out hundreds of other data, right?
So we can produce incredible quantities of data per user per day.
It's really, really hard to get that, okay?
For every one of the students, we can figure out within a few hours what they're strong at
and what they're weak at at the beginning of the course, right?
So we can produce a unique syllabus for each student each day, literally unique.
There's not enough time in the universe for any two students to have the same syllabus on any one day.
So we know you're going to fail. We know it in advance and we can prevent it in advance.
Let's go find a group of people who are psychometrically equivalent to that kid.
They learn the same ways, they have the same learning styles, they know the same stuff
because Newton can figure out things like you learn math best in the morning between 8.40 and 9.13 a.m.
You learn science best in 42-minute bite sizes.
The 44-minute market click rate always begins to decline.
You start missing questions. You normally get right.
You learn social studies best with video clips or 22% video to 78% text or whatever your optimal cocktail of fun.
We literally have more data about our students than any company has about anybody else, about anything.
This is a course at ASU. They had to change their semester structure into a modular semester structure
because we were suddenly telling things like if you give this woman here the final right now, she'll get an A.
It's only 14 days into the course. I promise you she'll get an A.
They all look like fleas, but that's all in an individual learning path.
Notice that some of them are going really fast, some are going really slow.
You can look at some of those students and think, boy, that poor schmuck is really in a lot of trouble.
So where we think we're going with this, talk about it as kind of a joke, but it really should work, is like a food diary.
You tell us what you had for breakfast every morning at the beginning of the semester.
By the end of the semester, we should be able to tell you what you had for breakfast
because you always do better on the days you have scrambled eggs.
And more importantly, we should be able to tell you what you should have for breakfast.