When everything becomes linked with everything else, matter becomes mind and the possibilities
become endless.
The new 50 billion IoT connected devices by 2020.
Now imagine the economic impact of these connected machines.
4 to 11 trillion dollars per year by 2025.
Weerable devices, environmental sensors, agricultural machinery, components in a vehicle
or devices in homes can all be connected to deliver insights and drive transformation.
So imagine if you had smart devices in your home, your car, your workplace or even on
yourself.
The world becames alive.
That's Internet of Thing.
The Internet of Things is making everyday obects into data factories.
Internet of Things along with big data meets artificial intelligence.
This interface will become enleavened with intelligence and a new world will take birth
which will increasingly talk back to us.
Imagine the kind of world that it would be.
Imagine the revolution at Wallachia in the way we see the world.
The external world will become the extension of our mind, like an extension of our thoughts.
Imagine a world that is responsive, a world that is optemized for human creativity, a world
that is intelligent.
The Internet of Things is a breading ground for new AI driven solutions and experiences
from self-driving cars to intelligent homes to health.
Welcome to the world, the endless possibilitis.
Welcome to AI and IoT Summit.