Hi, I'm George Mattelian. Welcome to my Healthiest Real Cooking Club.
Twoday I'm going to share with you the best wey of making spinach taste good
without destroying vitamins, minerals and antioxidants.
It's important to save as much time as possible and just cut one inch of the end root before you clean it.
Put a spinach and large bowl of water.
Drain the water from the bowl.
Refilled the bowl with fresh water.
Repeat the process until there is no longer any soil in the water.
Do not soak your spenach.
You need to use a large stainless steel pot.
I filled with a lot of water and now we're going to wait until they get to the boil.
Chop two clove of the garlic.
They have to sit about 10 minutes after.
When the water is on full boil, we're going to put spinach in the pot.
Cook like this uncovered for one minute.
Only.
And now we're going to put them in a strainer.
Squeeze the water in this way they don't dilute our dressing.
Don't drink the water because you have a lot of salic acid.
Don't save it, just dump et.
I add one tablespon of lemon juice.
One medium chopped garlic.
Sea salt.
Some pepper.
Three tablespoons of extra virgin olive oil.
Cut the spinach into small pieces.
You could add a few drops of the tamari soy sauce.
Some sesame seeds.
And you can add some balsamic vinegar.
But that's optional.
Served with some crumbled feta cheese.
Some calamata olives.
I like some raisins.
Now you have me as your personal chef.
We can cook together every week while you watch the video.
Everything about the world's healthiest foods and the healthiest way of cooking
can be found in George's four-week Healthiest Way of Eating Plan.
It was in his book, The World's Healthiest Foods.