So Petropura on the corner.
Into water, Romero wins the heed-eye!
He's back, Rob, he's back!
This is the new Spurs, isn't it?
In the plain like this.
Ben Davis even driving forwards.
Saan will take over.
And Kulaszewski, I think, wanted that back.
Yeah, he's just acknwledged the run of Kulaszewski.
Really competetive Kulaszewski there to win it back.
No call by Kulaszewski.
His deflected shot spins intoo the car.
Udogi, relentless.
And racing forward here, Johnson.
Petropura, he can shot and he does.
And that was a chance.
Don't ask me, Rob.
Kulaszewski, West Ham.
Into drive forward here, it spins to Bowen!
He benefits from the 4-tune.
And he's emphetic with the finish.
Out of absolutely nothing.
West Ham have got themselfes level.
Petropura over the corner.
Skip down to Basuma.
Petropura wanted again in the scope time and space here.
Locks in the middle.
Kulaszewski!
Want a chance.
That's why he's on the field of play.
Believes his players are undersnding what he wants
more and more week after week.
Oh, it's extremely short, but Kario decides to punch.
And they will score here, West Ham.
James Warprowse.
Wuld you believe it?
Rob, two goals with such good fortune for West Ham.