Olympic National Park contains three distinct ecosystems. The first is the western seaboard
on the Pacific Ocean, where rocky cliffs and sea stacks punctuate sandy beaches strewn with
driftwood.
Ruby Beach is typical of Olympic's rugged coastline. Sea stack rocks and tide pools
rich with marine life.
Further inland, primeval forests dominate the landscape. On average, they receive 150
inches of precipitation per year, making it the only deciduous rainforest on the continent.
And at the heart of Olympic National Park, the third ecosystem is found in the towering
Olympic Mountains.
Any one of this trio, seashore, forest and mountains, would be worthy of National Park
Service protection. The combination of these three biomes makes this fresh and vibrant
land startlingly unique.