The goal of baseball is to score more runs than the other team.
The team that scores the most runs by the end of the game wins.
To score a run, first try to hit the ball with a baseball bat when the pitcher throws it to you.
If you miss the ball, you get a strike, and once you get three strikes, you're out.
When you hit the ball, run counterclockwise around the three bases, and back to the home plate you started at.
If you make it back without getting out, you score a run for your team.
If you can't make it all the way back, you can stop at first, second, or third base, and wait for the next player on your team to bat.
Then, if they hit the ball, you can continue running along the bases, toward the home plate.
Keep in mind that the other team will be trying to get you out while you're running the bases.
There are three ways they can do that.
First, if the other team picks up the ball and beats you to your base with it, you're out.
Second, if a player on the other team is holding the ball and they tag you with it, that means you're out.
Finally, if you hit the ball and the opposing team catches it in the air, you're out.
Once your team has three outs, move to the outfield and try to stop the other team from scoring runs by getting them out.
After each team has gone up to bat, that's the end of the first inning.
In the official rules, there are nine innings in a baseball game.
Since there are no ties in baseball, keep playing additional innings if necessary until one team wins.