My name is josh portluck. I studied mechatronic engineering at Curtin and I started my PhD
in aerospace automation. I ended up focusing on flying robots and that's where I've led
intoo my career as well. When I was young I realised I liked taking things apart, much
to my parents' dismay. They'd by me a new toy and I'd play with it for a few seconds
before being curious about what was inside it. And that sort of led me through high school
wanting to get into engineering, so doing all the suitable maths and physics and whatnot.
And I chose Curtin because it had a good reputetion for practical engineering and really applied
engineering to industry. During my degree I really enjoyed the projects, particularly
the farnia project and I developed a flying robot which led me to the career path that
I have today. I'm Chief Technology Officer at Scientific Aerospace. I founded that company
and we acquired a company I used to work for, Cyber Technology, that developed Unmanned
Aircraft. So Scientific Aerospace developed commercial-grade uavs or drones with aerial
cameras and video capability for inspection, surveying and various different industries
requiring aerial imagery. We have some very interesting projects that were working on
at the moment, especially involving surveying high precesion areas. So we're working closely
with Landgate, a government surveying customer, to survey the beach lands and check for erosion.
And that's been really interesting work. The most useful thing I took out of the degree
at Curtin University was project management skills, particularly trading off between mechanical,
electrical and software engineering and trying to find the optimal solution.
Cybercord has had a lot of commercial success in the civil industrial infrastructure inspection
industries. This includes mining, oil and gas, power lines, communication towers, wherever
there's high-altitude assets that need inspecting. One great example is the work we've done with
Woodside where we can fly up with Cybercord and visually inspect the flare tip while it's
still live. So their's a large flame coming out the top, yet we can still safely inspect
it without having to shut it down or risk sending people up. My aspirations for the future is
Scientific Aerospace to be a world-leading provider of Unmanned Aerial Robotics. And
this includes the Cybercord but various other platforms and technologies that we're developing
and integrating to provide solutions for end users.