Do you want to be buzing like the bees?
Well, you're in the right place because today I'm going to show you how to make honey wine at home a.k.a.
mead and just the time of the time that traditional mead making takes all thanks to Bruzy. So meat is a honey wine
It's gluten-free delicious and good for the bees. The Vikings used to drink it too
So that's kind of cool gets your biking on. It's pretty simple to make all you need is your gallon jug honey water and your
Bruzy bag. I started off by heating up two-thirds of the gallon of water and adding my honey
You are what you drink so Im gonna make a sweet me
I added three cups of honey into my water and let it dissolve
Then you let the mixture cool until it reaches room temperature
These stuff is really important because we don't want to kill the yeast with too hot of water
Now all that's left to do is add your Bruzy bag shake well and keep it in a warm and dark place for seven days to ferment
So well be back in one week with an update. Stay tuned. Cheers