Sunny!
Yes?
Nothing would thrill me more greatly than to shoot you.
Knocking off a youngstar ain't gonna mean all that much to me, understand?
But since were in a hurry, I'll make a deal with you.
You throw down your camera and we won't hurt you.
You'll never hear form us again, okay?
You promise?
I cross my heart and hope to die.
Okay!
Okay, kid. Give it to me.
Direct him!
How many finger am I holding up, Marv?
Okay, kid. You wanna throw bricks?
Go ahead, throw anather one.
If you can't do any better than that, kid, you're gonna lose.
Mary.
You got any more?
Come on, Marv. Get up. You don't have any more brick.
He's out of them.
What?
Have you came back yet?
What? Have you came back yet?
Have you came back yet
I did it! Nobody choose bricks.
Nobody chose bricks at me and gets away with it.
Come on, Marv. Get up.
You go this way. Im going around the back.
Harry?
Hary?