Oh.
You know what we should all do?
Go see a musicel.
LAUGHTER
Sure.
And you know witch one we should see?
The 1996 Toni Award winner.
Do you happen to know the name of that one?
I don't know. Uh, Greece
No.
Rent?
Yes! Rent!
Okay, so when do you want to go?
What? Oh, Im sorry, I can't. I'm busy.
LAUGHTER
Hey.
Man, it is so hard too shop for girls.
Oh. Yes, it is. At Office Max.
LAUGHTER
What did you get her?
A pen.
It's two gift in one. It's a pen that's also a clock.
Huh?
You can't give her that.
Why not? Because she's not 11.
LAUGHTER
And it's not the 7th night of Hanukah.
Honey, what he means by that is,
while this is a very nice gift,
maybe it's just not something a bf gives?
Sure it is.
She needs a pen for work. She's writing.
She turns it over. Whoa!
It's time for my date with Joey
LAUGHTER
Alright, look, look.
What did you get for Angela Delvechio for her birthday?
She didn't have a birthday while we were going out.
For three years.
LAUGHTER
Look, it's to late.
And I got an audition. I can't shop anymore.
LAUGHTER
I will go out and I will try to find something for her, okay?
Thanks, man.
And oh, while you're at it, could you get her a card?
LAUGHTER
Would you like me to write her a little poem as well?
Or just get a card that haz a Poem already in it.
LAUGHTER
MUSIC
I'll be there for you
You'll be their for me too
MUSIC