What is quantum computing?
Quantum computing is a new type of computing architecture.
They'll make our devices millions of times faster than they are today.
In order to solve a problem, today's computer must run through all possible solutions
until it finds a single one that works.
For example, if we're looking for a name in a phone book with seven billion names,
we'd have to go through each name one by one until we found a match.
Similarly, classical computers work using bits,
single pieces of information that exists either a one or a zero.
Quantum bits or Q-bits, however, can exist as both a zero and a one simultaneously.
This means a quantum computer can check all possible solutions to a problem at one time.
For example, just 30 Q-bits can simulate 2 to the 30 or 1 billion possibilities in a split second.
And this is awesome for solving huge problems that are virtually an infinite number of possible answers.
Problems that simply cannot be solved by today's computers.
But this same superpower will also pose a major threat to cybersecurity.
The encryption algorithms of today rely on massive math problems that are near impossible to solve,
like factoring numbers hundreds of digits long.
A single quantum computer, however, could easily decrypt any piece of sensitive information
and render our entire system of cybersecurity obsolete.
That said, quantum computers will likely also allow us to create new quantum methods of encryption.
So I'm not too worried about that.
Still, that begs the question, will the first quantum computer be used for good or evil?