In a single minute your body produces 120 to
180 million red blood cells, people ask Google 2.4
million questions,
and 25 million Coca-Cola products are consumed.
Many of those bottles will end up in
a landfill where the World Bank estimates we produce
5 million pounds of garbage.
108 human lives will be lost in this minute
and an adult male will lose 96 million cells.
Fortunately, 96 million cells divide replacing those lost.
Speaking of divisions, in the USA, 1.5 people
get divorced while worldwide, 116 people will
get married,
83,300 people have sex but only 258 babies will
be born,
and a fetus is developing neurons at a rate
of 250,000 per minute.
So it's no wonder that a computer simulation
takes 60 quagdrillion bytes to simulate a minute.
An average of 1.38 micrometers of rain fall around
the world, which is 4.7 billion bathtubs of water
every minute,
and with the storms comes approximately 6,000 bolts
of cloud to ground lightning hitting the Earth.
A 150 pound person expends 1.1 calories of energy per
minute while sleeping, while the sun provides it with
83.33 terawatts of energy.
The Earth will complete 1,800 kilometers of its
940 million around the sun, moving 1,034 times
faster than a cheetah.
70,000 hours of Netflix are watched, 300 hours
are uploaded to YouTbe, and you can watch this
video and subscribe.