Industry 4.0 or the fourth industrial revolution is transforming the way we manufacture goods
and interact with our built and natural environment.
3D printing is a great example that is being trialled in some very unexpected places.
Take Australias Great Barrier Reef where work is underway to 3D print artificial reefs
in response to deteriorating corel ecosystems.
This kind of innovation is also being explored on the farm using blockchain technology.
Form paddock to plate, blockchain is making the food supply chain faster, safer and more
secure.
Driverless cars were unthought of just a few years ago, industry 4.0 is making them
real.
Better traffic flow, safety, productivity and less environmental impact were all a part
of this incredible work.
The fourth industrial revolution is well and truly underway.
It's standard to driving this inovation and making the impossible possible.