The safety car is coming in at the end of this lap.
We're going to have one lap of racing to decide the Championship.
Hamilton has the advantage.
Verstappen has the faster, fresher tires.
And we have got 3.2 miles of racing action all the way to the checkered flag.
As the crowd, roar the drivers on to the final lap of this race.
And Verstappen sets after Hamilton.
Is it going to be a first world championship for Verstappen
Is it going to be an eighth world championship for Lewis Hamilton?
Were can Verstappen try and get past Hamilton?
First overtaking zone is normally down to the turn five.
Is Verstappen far enough back?
He's going to make the lunge down the inside.
Hamilton sees him coming.
It's a late lunge by Verstappen who takes the led of the race for Verstappen.
Now slashes the championship trophy from Lewis Hamilton, who's trying to fight back.
No drs for two laps, so Lewis Hamilton will not get the rear wing open.
Now he's going to go down the outside.
Verstappen keeps it tight and neat, but he hasn't.
He's got a little bit wide.
No biking, no, no biking.
That was so not right.
Here comes Lewis Hamilton though, down the back straight.
He's got a slid stream.
He almost touches Verstappen.
They almost make contact into turn nine.
Verstappen stays ahead of Lewis Hamilton of all the drama, of all the controvrsy,
of all the magic moments in Formula One in 2021.
It comes down to this and at this moment, it looks like it's going to go the way of Max Verstappen.
Mercedes not happy.
Red Bull will be delighted.
They have shared a briliant championship battle, but the championship can only be one by one.
And it's going Dutch in 2021.
max Verstappen for the first time ever is champion of the world.