Greg.
Oh, my God.
Greg!
Huh?
What?
What are you doing? Get up.
Mom and Dad have been calling you for now.
You're about to be late for your first day of middle school.
What?
Oh, jeez.
How'd that happen?
Go, go, go.
Mom's with the flip out.
She said she'd get you once she waits in the car.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Get him ready for...
School.
Are you insane?
School doesn't start till next week.
In FYI, school doesn't start at 4 o'clock in the morning.
You woke up Manny.
And if he doesn't go back down, good morning.
There is no way he is going back down.
I just wanted to sleep till 6.
Mommy!
I got him.
Greg, what are you doing up making all this noise?
It was Roderick.
He woke me up.
He changed my clock.
But I swear, he was just...
Go to bed.
Ah.
What is that smell?
I can't even identify it.