Now the secret behind any great burger of course is in the colour making sure you've
got a nice beautiful colour on that burger patty. Get that pan nice and warm. In we go.
Again season it. Salt and pepper. As that starts caramelising a little touch of butter in there
just add more and more flavour. Start off at medium high heat. Turn it down and use the
remaining heat in that pan to continue cooking that burger beautifully. You can see that the
actual patty is starting to caramelise. You only flip burgers once, okay. Have the confidence
use the pan. Let the pan do the work and get that beautiful colour in there. I'm just going
to give that a little baste there. You can see what's happening up and over. Look at that colour.
Touch more butter. And because I've got all that beautiful heat in the pan, look, you can get my
onions in there and beautifully caramelise these onions. Season the other side of the burgers.
Season the onions. Again fresh cracked pepper. And now this whole thing is starting to come
together. Turn over my onions. Beautiful. The flavour and the smell is incredible. We're
literally cooking the burger two minutes each side. I like my burgers just under medium.
Before I put my cheese on, I like to season the burger again. Cheese on. Season the cheese.
And again, one more on top. And then from there, touch of fresh pepper. How do we melt that cheese
properly? First of all, turn off the heat. Get your lid. Stick that on top. And that will help
melt that cheese beautifully. Set that to the side. And now for the exciting part. This is where
we start to build this beautiful burger. My buns are being toasted, okay. So that's going to give
me a little bit more crispiness on there as well. First of all, a little smear of mayonnaise.
Soft butter lettuce. Just don't slice it. Just crack that open. Let that sit nicely. Again,
layer it up. Touch of salt. Touch of pepper. It goes a long way. Tomato on. And again,
a little touch of mustard. A beautiful Dijon mustard. And just rub that on the top part of
my bun. And then from there, I need some acid. I've got my pickles now. We're ready. Lid off.
Look at that cheese. It's melted beautifully. You can still hear that cook taking place inside
the pan. That's going to sit on top. And then finally, these onions, look at them. Caramelized,
beautifully. I just love the flavor. I just like to hit that with a touch of fresh pepper. And then,
bang. Now come on. That is a burger to die for.