Oh no. What?
I've got to leave for a date in two minutes.
What's the problem then?
Well I really want to have some two minute noodles.
Gee that is a slim time frame.
I'm not going to be able to cook two minute noodles,
which takes two minutes,
and then eat them,
which takes another one minute.
Fear not, I have the solution.
What is it?
I've been hiding a secret brother.
You've been hiding a secret brother?
No.
Where is he?
No, I've been-
Arnold!
No, I've been hiding a secret brother.
Who the f*** is Arnold?
Well what's the secret?
I can make two minute noodles in one minute.
What?
Where'd you come from?
The audacity of that statement conjured me out of thin air.
Wait, wait, so let me get this straight.
You reckon you can make two minute noodles in one minute?
Yes.
Well now you're just speaking gobbledygook.
I have magic abilities.
Magic abilities?
That's not real.
Darcy, you just appeared out of thin air.
Are you saying you're a wizard?
I'm just saying that there's a special spell.
Get on to it, we're running out of time.
Blitz and Blanton make this water hot as f***.
Wow, that was instant.
I can probably make my date now.
We did it.
We did it!
How long have you guys been talking?
Oh, at least a minute and a half.
You'd almost be further along the two minute noodle journey
if you just did it without all this magic.
Wimmy-d-d-blammy-d, shut the f*** up, Eddie.
Magic doesn't work on me.
What?
Guys, this video is supposed to be about noodles.
Why does magic not work on you, Darcy?
Because as magic law states, you can't use magic on your own brother.
Arnold!
It is I, Arnold.
Guys, we've completely lost the noodle plot line.
This is the secret brother you've been hiding.
This video is supposed to be about noodles.
I can't believe it, Arnold, you're home.