Get ready for things you want to know.
You probably know Simba from the Lion King movie.
But did you know that Simba means lion in Swahili?
And crowned king of the jungle because of its power and presence.
Found mostly in Sub-Saharan Africa,
lions have a special sense of family
and are the only big cats that prefer to live in groups called a pride.
A family unit with up to three males,
a dozen females and their young, often all related,
with as many as 15 lions.
The lionesses certainly have their paws full as the primary hunters of their pride.
These queens and princesses like to stick together to help make their royal pride strong.
Using stealth and strategy,
female lions often work together to bring down prey.
And while the queens are out hunting for food,
the kings of the jungle are likely taking their long daily nap.
Male lions spend about 18 to 20 hours a day sleeping.
When they're not sleeping,
they're protecting their pride and their territory,
using their powerful roar that they don't gain until two years of age.
Lions are 25 times louder than a gas-powered lawnmower.
Both the kings and queens of the jungle play an important role
in keeping their royal family healthy and safe.
So Simba, his lionesses and the rest of the pride
definitely cause an uproar in the wild.