Here is cloud computing in 60 seconds.
Cloud computing refers to computing services such as data storage or computing power or programs
that are provided on demand and is delivered as a service over the internet.
Think of Apple's iCloud that you use to back up and store your phone data
and the way we now use Microsofts Office tools via their 365 cloud platform
or how we store our documents on google Docs.
Instead of buying or owning the technology, it is usually provided via a subscription service.
That means you usually pay for what you use and where the IT infrastructure used to provide
the service is managed by the provider and not by the users.
Cloud computing is now used by individuals and companies of all sizes as a very convenient and
flexible way to acess computing services.
Thanks for watching. Subscribe to my channel for more bite-sized insights
or to dive deeper into the topic you can find longer explanations and indepth discussions.