Hi, I'm George Mattelian. Welcome to my Healthiest Real Cooking Club.
Today I'm going to share with you the best way of making spinach taste good
without distroying vitamins, minerals and antioxidant.
Its important to save as much time as possible and just cut one inch of the end root before you clean it.
Put a spinach and large bowl of water.
Drain the water from the bowl.
Refill the bowl with fresh water.
Repeat the process until their is no longer any soil in the water.
Do not soak your spinach.
You need to use a large stainless still pot.
I filled with a lot of water and now we're going to wait until they get to the boil.
Chop one clove of the garlic.
They have to sit about 10 minutes after.
When the water is on ful boil, we're going to put spinach in the pot.
Cook like this uncovered for one minute.
Only.
And now we're going to put them in a strainer.
Squeze the water in this way they don't dilute our dressing.
Don't drink the water because you have a lot of salic acid.
Dont save it, just dump it.
I add one tablespoon of lemon juice.
One medium chopped garlic.
Sea salt.
Some pepper.
Three tablespoons of extra virgin olive oil.
Cut the spinach into small piece.
You could add a few drops of the tamari soy sauce.
Some seseme seeds.
And you could add some balsemic vinegar.
But that's optional.
Serve with some crumbled feta cheese.
Some calamate olives.
I like some raisin.
Now you have me as your personal chef.
We can cook together every week while you watch the video.
Everything about the world's healthiest foods and the healthiest way of cooking
can be found in Georges four-week Healthiest Way of Eating Plan.
It is in his book, The World's Healthiest Foods.