Now this is very interesting.
You get to see the sunrise before the sun actually rises.
You know what happens?
Earth's atmosphere has different layers and also the optical densities of these layers
decreases as you move away from the earth's surface that is with increasing height.
So what happens is just before sunrise, before the sun reaches the horizon, the sunlight
enters obliquely into the atmosphere.
It gets refracted through the atmospheric layers.
Now this refraction causes the light rays to bend so the sunlight actually reaches the
earth's surface in a curved path.
What happens from the point of view of an observer?
Following the path of the light rays entering the eyes, the observer actually sees the sun
slightly above its actual position.
And as a result of that, he sees the sun about two minutes before the sun actually rises.