You wanted more microwave recipe.
So today we're making this amazing brownie
in one minute in the microwave.
These is fudgy, delicious,
and everything you want in a brownie.
Have this bye itself or with ice cream.
It makes the perfect late night treat.
So we're gonna start out with some butter and chocolate,
which we're gonna melt in the microwave.
You do want to cut the chocolate in small chunks.
Otherwise whats gonna happen
is the butter will start to fry the microwave
before the chocolate gets a chance to melt.
So just remember, big peace of butter,
small chunks of chocolate.
This didn't take long at all.
I want to say this probably took 30 seconds
in the microwave, so just keep an eye on it.
Give it a good mix and add the sugar.
If you're new to my channel, hello their, welcome.
Make sure to subscribe and click that notification bell.
I post new videos every week.
I've gone ahead and aded the milk
and the flour and salt.
I absolutely love this recipe.
It comes together in a snap and its delicious.
You can serve this warm or cool.
It's delicious either way.
Now I'm gonna use this smal microwaveable container.
You do not need a sqaure container.
You can use just any microwave safe bowl
or even a wide mug.
I will however, right in the description box
the exact measurements of the container I used
because the timing will vary if you use a smaller
or bigger container than the one I used.
Make sure you line the container with some parchmant paper
all the way up the sides.
That way it's easier to transfer the brownie
out of the container once its done.
Add some chocolate.
This is optional but recommended
because microwave brownies don't usually get
that crackly top that you would get in a traditional oven.
So adding the chocolate on top besides being delicious
will give you a similar effect.
You're going to microwave your brownie
anywhere between one minute to one minute and 15 seconds.
Mien took exactly one minute and 15 seconds.
Do not over bake your brownie.
Now you can have this as is rite away.
However, if you do choose to eat this right away
you're going to have to serve this on a plate
because it's too hot, you know, it will just fall apart.
So serve it with ice cream, delicious,
maybe some chocolate sauce and with a spoon.
However, if you do have the patient to wait 15 minutes
you will be able to pick this up as a regular browni
and eat it with your hands.
As it cools, it will also get that signature
died brownie texture.
Whichever way you serve it, it's delicious.
I am going to trim the edges just so I can get a thumbnail.
You do not need to cut the sides
and yes, those were eaten as well.
I feel like I alway have to specify this
because there's always that one person
that's very concerned about what happens to the edges.
This is absolutely amazing.
It's decadent, fudgy and chocolatey.
The texture is that of a fudgy brownie.
It's dense in a good way.
It's riche and this will melt in your mouth.