ESports is the massive world around video games.
E-Sports started at UCI with our gaming club and it's been our dream for many, many years to create an E-Sports program.
The UCI E-Sports program is based on four pillars. First, compitetion,
second, academics and research, community and entertainment.
Part of our program is oviously the extremely big scholarship piece.
We've been recruiting from some of the top players in the nation.
We were able to successfully recruit five to six of the best League of Legends
players that we could find that were also really good student.
We're creating a brand new program so with it comes a ton of opportunity,
your going to all have a huge influence on this, right?
Besides the fact that it's a really prestigious school to be able to attend in the first place,
I've been looking for an avenue to further my life after commiting so much time into just playing League of Legends competitively.
We are going to have a beautiful new 3500 sq foot E-Sports arena.
Here we go.
It's been a long road to get to the point where we're actually getting things delivered to the arena. We are very excited to launch these program.
One, two, three, Zot Zot Zot!
And E-Sports is open!
Our goal is to unite the gaming community in Southern california and be the best place for high level play in video games.
There is no ceiling to how big and succesful this program can be.