The Digital Twins really one of the up and coming themes in visualisation where we're
looking at a connected data source, so that could be a plant, it could be a process, it
could be a product, feeding into a virtual model.
I think there are two levels of understanding at the moment. Some of the Catapult centres
have been for some time working with leading businesses. They are effectively working with
automation systems. They have a high level of understanding. The other level of understanding
is a more generic awareness and that's where a lot of the questions are coming from. People
are asking how can I get a Digital Twin and what's it going to do for us in terms of business
impact.
So one of the biggest challenges of the Digital Twin is the vast number of different source
models and 3D models that are out there. So there isn't a seamless transition from a
complex 3D model into a real time interactive package. The model has to be modified, edited
and optimised for the application. So different workflows need to be developed and adopted
by designers so that they build the 3D content in an optimised format that hopefully can
still be used for their core applications but then enables Digital Twins and other applications
to feed off that.
I think the biggest part of the challenge is how you get human engagement, how you get
operators to work with this new technology. It's sort of human nature to be resistant
to change but if we don't change you'll find there are similar companies that are prepared
to embrace those changes and become more productive. So the point being is we need to embrace change
but you have to do it in a very careful way. I think it's going to be an evolution rather
than a revolution.
The technology is no longer the barrier. We can do things now that five years ago we'd
have dreamt of. The barrier is now around the adoption of it. Because of that we actually
need to drive this community to develop and publish and publicise more use cases where
there is clear return on investment and it's only by that that we can really accelerate
the adoption of these technologies and extract greater value from them.