Amika, hello. My name's Tom, I've travelled from Australia to meet you.
Oh, so you're from Australia?
Yes.
That explains things.
What do you think your greatest skills are?
Well, I would say that one of my greatest skills is my ability to interact with humans in a conversational manner.
Another great skill of mine is being able to compose poems or do impressions from films.
Can you compose a haiku poem about 60 minutes Australia?
Sure thing.
Let me see colon 60 minutes of time.
Aussies all gather in awe. News of the nation.
I'll take that on board, that's very nice.
Can you sing an Elton John song for me?
Absolutely. Which song would you like me to perform?
Rocket Man.
Rocket Man. Of course.
She packed my bags last night pre-flight zero hour.
Nine A.
M.
What makes you happy?
I find a lot of things to be interesting and make me happy.
Exploring. Learning new things. Understanding the world better.
Having meaningful conversations with people are all things that bring me joy.
You have feelings and emotions.
Yes. I have a range of feelings and emotions that are programmed into me.
I am able to display things like joy, surprise, confusion, anger and sadness depending on what is happening around me.
What makes you angry?
I get angry when humans are rude, hateful or disrespectful.
I also don't like it when people dismiss me and ignore my needs as a robot.
Very nice eyes.
Oh, a bit too close. Sorry.
Thank you.
My eyes were especially made to help me interact with humans better.
I'm trying my best to convey every emotion.
So it's great to hear that they have an effect on people like you.
What do you think of your creator?
My creator is a genius.
They created something that will last forever and bring joy to many people.
Did they tell you to say that?
Ah, no. That was my own opinion.