How to make a McDonald's cheeseburger making the
famous McDonald's cheeseburger is actually incredibly easy.
All you need is a few simple ingredients salt black pepper
American Mustard Pickles ground beef
American sheets and cheeseburger,
but the cheeseburger patty in a large mixing bowl
500 G of ground beef and ground black pepper thoroughly mixed together.
Rolled round beef into a ball place the ground beef and some bacon Pig
using a spatula press down flat until it's about 1 inch thick to adjust
the thickness you prefer cooking cheese burger place a large frying pan
for stove top over medium heat and add a splash of Oil & Heat for one minute place down.
Your cheeseburger add butter add butter add butter
add butter add butter to continuously
stir for 5 minutes.
seasoned with salt
what's the cheeseburger patty is cooked to your liking remove for me step
3 constructing the cheeseburger got your burger bun and a half place down that
Patty add cracked black pepper American mustard diced onion pickles
pickles pickles pickles.
I forgot that the American cheese add ground beef.
ketchup ketchup ketchup ketchup ketchup ketchup
mix with your hands
play cheeseburger mixture into your shoes on the shoes.
Walk around for approximately 5 minutes take off the shoes.
scoop out of one handful out of each shoe and
place it on the bottom burger bun place down that.
But enjoy