Playoff time, baby.
Games, snacks, drink.
I mean, what else can you ask for, bro?
Really?
Hey, pass me a pepsi.
I mean, can you drink any louder?
Thats how I drink.
Loud like that?
I drink loud.
I like to enjoy it.
Tos me some ways.
Did you eat any louder?
It's normal to eat loud.
Drinking loud makes no sense.
BAM!
Hayden!
Eli!
Road trip!
Hard pass.
Playoff are on.
You're paying for that door, by the way.
I got a bus!
The bus has got a bus!
Let's go!
Can we go see the bus?
What up, Eli?
Mr Cruz!
I miss you, buddy.
I miss you too, man.
Super Bowl, baby.
Let's go!
We're not going.
I'm going to get more chips and drinks.
Do not live this room.
I got you.
Whoa!
Super Bowl!
Here we go!
Are you kidding me?
Technically, I didnt leave the room.
I'll call her mom.
After I finish these chips.
How much longer?
You drive weird.
Bus, are we their yet?
No!
Hey, bus, we got to pull over for some more chips and drinks.
Oh, you got it.
Hey, guys, look who I found.
Bradshaw?
Hey, guys, got room for one more?
Got Doritos?
Got mountain Dew.
Do we really want to bring them?
They might start to feel crowded.
I mean, maybe if you had a little...
Oh, plz don't.
Don't say it.
Salsa.
I love me some salza.
All right, I got an idea.
We got one seat left, and it's special just for you.
Lets do it!
Ahhh!
It's like a convertible.
It's a hole lot better.
I lost my mind like something my way.
It's all my fault.
Just so Im naked, I really don't get it.
It does kind of open things up a little bit.