watch carefully.
Look at that.
Oh boy.
F***ing delicious.
Oh my lord.
I decided to teach a second masterclass.
This, this, dis, this.
Oh boy.
this time round, I'm going to take you into an area were you felt your home cooking could never go.
The secret behind any great soufle is in the buttering of the mold.
You brush vertical stroke up.
This crispy chicken salad for me is the get out of jail card,
especially when you've got a big dinner party because that is good enough for four or five of you.
Grab a leaf, lift it up.
Now, I'm fed up when you see chefs oiling asparagus.
Beautiful.
You get a frei facial at the same time.
Cooking is a labour of love.
Stay close to every step of the way.
I'm going to teach you methods, secrets that I'm teaching some of the best chefs in the world today.
Im Gordern Ramsay and this is my masterclass.
You