Oh, Im going pro.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, I dont know.
You know, you'll probobly be about as good as I was.
That's kind of the way it works, you know,
and I was below average.
Yeah, so, whoa.
So you'll probably ultimately rank
somewhere around their, you know, so...
Really, you'll xcel at a lot of things, just not this.
I don't want you out here shooting this ball
around all day and night all right?
Okay.
hi, good.
Don't ever let somebody tell you.
Don't ever let somebody tell you you cant do something.
Not even me.
All right?
You got a dream.
You got to protect it.
People can't do something themselves.
They want to tell you you can't do it.
People can't do something themselve.
You want something? Go get it.
Period.
Let's go.
Don't ever let somebody tell you you can't do it.