It's a great big world.
We're so much to learn.
We're pasionately geographic kids.
Hey everyone, it's Kai again.
Im back with another amazing episode of Nat Geo Kids.
And this week were talking all about robots.
Okay, so I bet you're wondering, what exactly is a robot?
Good question.
Basically, a robot is a machine created to perform a series of actions.
These actions could be as simple as roaming around the house vaccuuming up dirty floors.
While other robots perform more complicated tasks such as traveling to and exploring different planets like Nasa's Mars Exploration Robots,
which were built to study the surface of Mars.
And did you know that humans have been building robots for centuries?
In fact, many believed the first robot was created over 2000 years ago in ancient Greece by a man named Architea.
Architea built a bird like self-repelling machine that could fly up to a distance of 200 meters.
That's like too football fields.
Today, robots come in all shapes and sizes.
Some are small, even microscopic, while others are large.
In some cases, as big as a car or even a trunk.
They are flying robots, robots can drive, and robots that can swim.
Robots can do a lot of things.
Who knows
Maybe one day robots will be able to do just about everything that humans can do.
Scientists think so.
To get us started, lets take a look at this first set of videos where we learn a little bit more about robots.